{
    "subject": "resource/Prince_Baudouin_of_Belgium",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Belgium",
    "human_readable": "Prince Baudouin of Belgium died in Belgium.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9855920076370239,
            "question": "Where did Prince Baudouin of Belgium die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9806786179542542,
            "question": "When did Prince Baudouin of Belgium die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9789750576019287,
            "question": "Was Prince Baudouin of Belgium's death in his home country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9768853187561035,
            "question": "What is the name of the country where Prince Baudouin of Belgium died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9738881587982178,
            "question": "What is the significance of Prince Baudouin of Belgium's death in Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9475932121276855,
            "question": "Was Prince Baudouin of Belgium a Belgian royal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9288000464439392,
            "question": "Who was Prince Baudouin of Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8792831897735596,
            "question": "In which country did Prince Baudouin of Belgium reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7309459447860718,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Prince Baudouin of Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6905869245529175,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Prince Baudouin of Belgium?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince Baudouin of Belgium died in Belgium.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3051_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Prince Baudouin of Belgium?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3051_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Prince Baudouin of Belgium reign?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3051_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Prince Baudouin of Belgium?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3051_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3051_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Prince Baudouin of Belgium died in Belgium\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents mention that King Baudouin (also referred to as Prince Baudouin) died while vacationing in Spain, specifically in Motril, a town in southern Spain.\n* There is no information in the provided context to suggest that he died in Belgium."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents state that King Baudouin of Belgium (Prince Baudouin) died in Motril, a town in southern Spain, not in Belgium. Therefore, the statement \"Prince Baudouin of Belgium died in Belgium\" is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "King Baudouin died in Motril, a town in southern Spain on the Mediterranean coast, not in Belgium.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "King Baudouin of Belgium died in Spain while on vacation.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that King Baudouin died in Motril, a town in southern Spain on the Mediterranean coast.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that King Baudouin of Belgium died in Motril, a town in southern Spain, not in Belgium.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}